Dana Brown

My ultimate goal is to obtain a position that I can utilize my abilities as a web designer, but also become a member of a team in a positive environment that presents challenge and promotes growth. I have been working as a digital prepress mac operator and production artist for over 20 years. I have a diverse graphic arts background with roots in printing. I polished my skills in Photoshop, color correcting images, photo retouching and image manipulation. Over the years, I honed my design skills utilizing Adobe Creative Suite. With my diversified background, I bring a wide range of skills to the table, to some I am considered a 'jack of all trades.'

Qualifications

- Executes production of creative and graphic concepts from design team
- Produces technically correct, print-ready mechanicals for release
- Follows projects throughout all stages of print production and/or online deployment
- Interacts regularly with designers and other team members as needed for completion of assigned projects
- Solves business challenges through smart production
- Takes ownership, leads initiatives and successfully executes through all stages of production development on target, on time and on budget
- Maintains and enhances the client's identity by working within the corporate Brand
- Manages the execution of the work, ensuring that creative projects are completed on time
- Effectively use project management system to track time on all projects
- Understands the client's design needs and methodology
- Communicates effectively with peers, senior management and clients across all topics from business to creative

Skillset

XHTML/CSS Knowledge of web design, search engine optimization, web standards, usability, and much more. Experience with JavaScript and PHP in the creation of dynamic web pages and responsive web design.

Dreamweaver Strong knowledge of site definition, email campaigns and web optimization.

Photoshop Strong knowledge of color correction, photo retouching and image manipulation. Ability to manipulate images utilizing layer masks and clipping paths and images for front-end web development.

Illustrator Expert skills in vector art creation from clean art to logos to photo tracing, gradients and diestrike creation for the printing industry.

InDesign Expert skills in creation of page layout and design, variable data, form and table creation, utilizing master pages and pagination, taking into consideration image resolutions for the printing industry as well as advanced pre-press procedures.

Acrobat Experience creating high resolution PDFs, interactive PDFs, workflow for the printing industry and web utilization.

Microsoft Office Working knowledge of word, powerpoint and excel.

Employment

Production Artist | Humana | Louisville, KY | 1/2017 to present
Operational Support Officer | Navy Personnel Command | Millington, TN | 12/2014 to 12/2016
Digital Pre-press | RR Donnelley/Commercial Press | San Diego, CA | 10/2005 to 12/2014

Education

Bachelor of Science, Media Arts/Web Design | Platt College, San Diego, CA | 09/2010 Associate of Art Degree | Lorain County Community College, Elyria, OH | 12/2001 Graphic Design | Kent State University, Kent, OH | 08/1987 to 12/1989

Military

I served in the Navy Reserve for 22 years, ultimately retiring December 1, 2016 at the rank of Chief Petty Officer. Throughout the course of my career I traveled the world, taking orders in the U.S. and outside the U.S., and deploying twice to the Middle East. I am an Afghanistan veteran, Operation Enduring Freedom veteran and Noble Eagle veteran.